Key insights from the paper, Comprehensive Health Data Analysis for Early
Dementure Diagnosis, a Machine Learning approach.
J. Min Salvi, Asterisk Operator, Agam Shah,
Asterisk Operator Department of Computer Science,
NIRMA University, India, Department of Computer Science, NIRMA University, India,
ABSTRACT.
This paper investigates the application of machine.
Learning.
Milliliter.
Models to predict dementia diagnosis using a Comprehensive Health Data Set.
The data set includes key health-related features such as diabetic status, heart rate,
blood oxygen, levels, body temperature, cognitive test scores, and lifestyle.
Factors.
We employed milliliter techniques to predict dementia onset.
Leveraging algorithms such as support vector machines.
SVM.
And Logistic Regression.
Our findings demonstrate that milliliter.
Models.
Particularly SVM and Logistic Regression.
Can effectively identify key predictors and achieve substantial accuracy in dementia
prediction.
The primary aim of this study is to validate.
The performance of milliliter models in detecting dementia at an early stage and to identify
the most influential health and cognitive.
Factors contributing to dementia risk.